<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes"?>
<rss xmlns:sparkle="http://www.andymatuschak.org/xml-namespaces/sparkle" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Batch Clipboard</title>
        <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/jpmhouston/Batch-Clipboard/main/appcast.xml</link>
        <description>Most recent changes with links to updates.</description>
        <language>en</language>
        <item>
            <title>2.0b3</title>
            <pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 15:42:52 +0000</pubDate>
            <link>https://github.com/jpmhouston/Batch-Clipboard/releases</link>
            <sparkle:channel>beta</sparkle:channel>
            <sparkle:version>2060</sparkle:version>
            <sparkle:shortVersionString>2.0b3</sparkle:shortVersionString>
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>10.15</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
            <description><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Now current batch menu item are always in natural order, top is most
recent to paste, even when history features are on.</li>
<li>Rebuilt the Intro window panel for transition from 1.0 and
confirming history on or off, improving layout to allow larger and more
descriptive text, no longer focus on the menu item order but instead
performance, simplicity, duplication of OS features.</li>
<li>Decided option to hde the menu bar icon should be for all versions
instead of only for in-app purchasers. Moved its setting from the
Advanced panel to the General panel and improved its layout.</li>
<li>Added a clarification to the Advanced panel in the Settings window
that saved batched are never cleared when to clear-history option it
turned on.</li>
<li>Fixed an issue where upon hiding the menu bar icon macOS forgets its
favored position in the menu.</li>
<li>Prepare for using a liquid-glass version of the app icon on macOS 26
Tahoe, original icon on older systems.</li>
</ul>
]]></description>
            <enclosure url="https://github.com/jpmhouston/Batch-Clipboard/releases/download/v2.0b3/Batch.Clipboard.2.0b3.zip" length="6215179" type="application/octet-stream" sparkle:edSignature="j84eUx1DUIb/5PveMzbOAuqmbUkW96e1mbrK0jc9stzWDyYMwDVXDZuIErPg0jFxoYr702mT+DhGCuXaKyX0DA=="/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>2.0b2</title>
            <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 16:11:18 +0000</pubDate>
            <link>https://github.com/jpmhouston/Batch-Clipboard/releases</link>
            <sparkle:channel>beta</sparkle:channel>
            <sparkle:version>2052</sparkle:version>
            <sparkle:shortVersionString>2.0b2</sparkle:shortVersionString>
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>10.15</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
            <description><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Added support for a beta channel to Sparkle updates in the non-app
store version, a checkbox in the General panel of the Settings window to
get betas in addition to final releases, a new menu item just below
About… when an update found. If the user cancels the update alert on
launch then they can use this menu item instead of going into the
Settings window.</li>
<li>Revise the menu items some more, tweaking the titles of several
items, changing which are shown and disabled when not applicable vs
hidden.</li>
<li>New extra feature for the app store releases, checkbox in the
Advanced panel of the Settings window to hide the menu bar icon when the
app has no active batch, or when the application re-opened in the Finder
(also causes the Settings window to open).</li>
<li>Fixes and improvements to the application intents accessible from
Shortcuts and Spotlight.</li>
</ul>
]]></description>
            <enclosure url="https://github.com/jpmhouston/Batch-Clipboard/releases/download/v2.0b2/Batch.Clipboard.2.0b2.zip" length="6204364" type="application/octet-stream" sparkle:edSignature="H973U2F87QuevHTyTn+dT7N3Dcn0QycntGpgMmgBKNdflNrOJl/i61vA95YoHT/vict0qld+IF6CSJniIY7HDQ=="/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>2.0b1</title>
            <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:30:47 +0000</pubDate>
            <link>https://github.com/jpmhouston/Batch-Clipboard/releases</link>
            <sparkle:channel>beta</sparkle:channel>
            <sparkle:version>2044</sparkle:version>
            <sparkle:shortVersionString>2.0b1</sparkle:shortVersionString>
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>10.15</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>A substantially new version with a lot of changes. TL;DR:</p>
<ul>
<li>a simpler and more efficient history-off mode is the new
default</li>
<li>a repeat last batch feature</li>
<li>in the app store version: saved batches</li>
<li>improved simplicity for the menu and settings window</li>
</ul>
<p>What’s listed below somewhat exhaustively includes the many changes
both visible and under the hood. The version notes in the release
version will instead be less complete, and a list more like what’s below
will be posted on the documentation website
batchclipboard.bananameter.lol.</p>
<ul>
<li>Implemented major feature: ability to turn history off for
simplicity and system effeciency, now the default.</li>
<li>When history off and without need to stay consistent with its
bottom-up order, ie. most recent at the top, the current batch is now
shown in top-down order, ie. first to paste at the top.</li>
<li>Migrating from 1.0.x to 2.0 shows a Intro page offering to switch to
the new history-off default or keep using history, the default for those
users is to keep using the history features unless they choose to switch
then or later in the Settings window Storage panel.</li>
<li>Implemented major feature: replaying previous batch again, and
support giving the menu item a keyboard shortcut (empty by
default).</li>
<li>Implemented major feature for app store version users who’ve made an
in-app purchase: saving current or previous batches, each can have an
optional keyboard shortcut. They appear in a new section of the menu
when there’s no current batch active, each with their clips in a submenu
and items to replay, rename. A saved batch or individual clips within
can be deleted with the same command-delete shortcut when the menu is
open.</li>
<li>Improved feature for app store version users who’ve made an in-app
purchase: in-between pasting multiple clips at a time from the current
batch, a new option to insert a space, newline, or comma.</li>
<li>By necessity, the Undo Last Paste feature for app store version
users who’ve made an in-app purchase is now removed in the new default
history-off mode.</li>
<li>Menu simplification: in new default history-off mode, no
complication of a different form of the menu when its opened with the
option key pressed.</li>
<li>Menu simplification: the Start Replaying and Advance menu items are
now hidden by default. They can be restore with an option in the
Settings window Advanced panel.</li>
<li>Menu simplification: the type-in filter history field, the one
that’s available in the expanded menu when history on for app store
version users who’ve made an in-app purchase, this is hidden by default
unless turned on in the Settings window Appearance panel.</li>
<li>Minor improvements to the menu: when deleting items from the menu
with command-delete the menu no longer closes, new title labels over
Current Batch, Saved History, Saved Batch sections.</li>
<li>Improved simplicity of how the menu is opened in reaction to clicks
in hopes of addressing possible failures, stripping some unused feature
of the old behavior inherited from Maccy. Added an option to the
Settings window Advanced panel for reverting to the old behavior in case
of incompatibilities.</li>
<li>Improved layout and location of options in Settings window panels:
new history switch and related menu size fields together in the Storage
panel, new or improved descriptive labels in the General, Appearance,
and Advanced panels.</li>
<li>Improved layout and language in the Intro window, including
descriptions of IAP-unlocked features in the app store version.</li>
<li>Unit tests to verify correct queue, history behavior, and also
general backing store correctness including migration from older
versions. Improved menu reliability with sanity checking and logging of
unexpected conditions.</li>
<li>Migrated source to new GitHub repository that isn’t a fork of
Maccy.</li>
</ul>
]]></description>
            <enclosure url="https://github.com/jpmhouston/Batch-Clipboard/releases/download/v2.0b1/Batch.Clipboard.2.0b1.zip" length="6145717" type="application/octet-stream" sparkle:edSignature="pZOdyPHO7zNt0b98svafTBn4qZDJu2VBRxqyFyNd0Zh+iuuSvw+aJj7R1/laROD91EZIK41rZY1hM1zW/m9AAQ=="/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>1.0.3</title>
            <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 02:02:15 +0000</pubDate>
            <link>https://github.com/jpmhouston/Cleepp/releases</link>
            <sparkle:version>965</sparkle:version>
            <sparkle:shortVersionString>1.0.3</sparkle:shortVersionString>
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>10.15</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
            <description><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Corrected some link desintations in the About and Intro
windows.</li>
</ul>
]]></description>
            <enclosure url="https://github.com/jpmhouston/Cleepp/releases/download/v1.0.3/Batch.Clipboard.1.0.3.zip" length="6743192" type="application/octet-stream" sparkle:edSignature="V2HYFxjejq7FX58ASWJESmSeIij5p5lFPB1OecWC9spAIlNgzukLJLESYETjlXlkBk4M6tQniVz9VG3uotlUCA=="/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>1.0.2</title>
            <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jun 2025 23:59:31 +0000</pubDate>
            <link>https://github.com/jpmhouston/Cleepp/releases</link>
            <sparkle:version>954</sparkle:version>
            <sparkle:shortVersionString>1.0.2</sparkle:shortVersionString>
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>10.15</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
            <description><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>Ship the 1.0.2b1 changes in time for WWDC 2025, defer fix for
sporadic crash until more reports available.</li>
<li>Changed the github workflow for the app store verison to also
automatically deploy when triggered by pushed tag matching the project’s
version (matching non-app store workflow behavior).</li>
</ul>
]]></description>
            <enclosure url="https://github.com/jpmhouston/Cleepp/releases/download/v1.0.2/Batch.Clipboard.1.0.2.zip" length="6737024" type="application/octet-stream" sparkle:edSignature="J83xcRZqAT26prIkM9vTvShNJvxTGPaSrPP7dtrtkWbqCnhpRPhbodK6Q6bDylGoNR0AYkGql3MMX8FF+iABCg=="/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>1.0.1</title>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 00:46:54 +0000</pubDate>
            <link>https://github.com/jpmhouston/Cleepp/releases</link>
            <sparkle:version>937</sparkle:version>
            <sparkle:shortVersionString>1.0.1</sparkle:shortVersionString>
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>10.15</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>First official release. For pre-release development history see github.com/jpmhouston/Cleepp/releases</p>
]]></description>
            <enclosure url="https://github.com/jpmhouston/Cleepp/releases/download/v1.0.1/Batch.Clipboard.1.0.1.zip" length="6733219" type="application/octet-stream" sparkle:edSignature="g6D8V6sfXWyu41l+VWa3WSQmTAnKqWXqvpX9JxPfKCyb9lNaWVLtgeL1jalNTq0D5YUghs1Bfd27ERzgZPT2CA=="/>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
